<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <generator uri="https://gohugo.io/" version="0.123.7">Hugo</generator>
    <title>News on Onigiri☆Onegai</title>
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/news/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="html" />
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/news/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" title="atom" />
    <updated>2024-04-04T12:08:09-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://onigirionegai.info/tags/news/</id>
        <entry>
            <title>April Fools</title>
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/post/april-fools/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"  hreflang="en" />
            <id>http://onigirionegai.info/post/april-fools/</id>
            <published>2024-04-04T09:04:49-07:00</published>
            <updated>2024-04-04T09:04:49-07:00</updated>
            <content type="html">
                
&lt;p&gt;
I finally did it! I made an April Fools joke. Okay, I don&amp;#39;t have analytics on this site so I don&amp;#39;t know who saw it but, no, we are not suddenly a chicken company. Actually it was kind of &lt;a href=&#34;http://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi&#34;&gt;Yayoi&amp;#39;s&lt;/a&gt; idea to make it a &amp;#34;Chimkin&amp;#34; site, but I added a few things because Easter also happened to be at a weird time this year due to us having a fifth Sunday in the month of March. Anyway, the joke&amp;#39;s over now back to our regularly scheduled programming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-1&#34;&gt;
April Fool&amp;#39;s and Why I Wanted to Participate
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those of you who aren&amp;#39;t aware. April Fools or Fool&amp;#39;s Day is a holiday we celebrate in the United States. I am actually not sure if it is celebrated elsewhere, if you are in a different country and celebrate April Fools, why not let me know. I&amp;#39;ve put up a &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jjon-saxton/onigiri/discussions/2&#34;&gt;Poll and Discussion&lt;/a&gt; thread to talk about your experiences with this day. Anyway, On this day its all about pranks and just generally spreading misinformation, of course, that&amp;#39;s now every day here in the US, but this &lt;em&gt;used&lt;/em&gt; to be the only day we did were allowed to lie and have it socially acceptable. I never participated, because, I&amp;#39;ll be honest, I never had any good ideas. As a scientist of sorts I am usually more interested in finding and spreading the truth and not misinformation so it was a bit difficult for me to think of something to do on April Fool&amp;#39;s day until this year actually. And, of course, credit where credit is due, it was not solely my idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-2&#34;&gt;
How Did This &amp;#34;Chimkin&amp;#34; Thing Get Started?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I approached the only other active member of Onigiri*Onegai and said I wanted to do something to the site for April Fool&amp;#39;s and she said she had a dream where she had started selling chicken sandwhiches and had come to me to build her a website so I said, why not do that? She liked the idea, but things hit a bit of a snag. I said I wanted to make sure it would work in old browsers so I was going to take down the Hugo we run. She wanted to make sure everything was reversable, so I said I wouldn&amp;#39;t take them down, but just change a few configuration files. I forgot exactly how I had set up the production server though, so, well things were a bit more tricky than I thought and took longer than I wanted. It also didn&amp;#39;t help that I forgot about this until the 1st. So what we ended up with wasn&amp;#39;t exactly what we wanted, but I think it did the trick for this year. I have assured Yayoi that things will be much more polished if we do this again next year. She seemed content with that. We&amp;#39;ll see if we do something like this again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-3&#34;&gt;
In Other News
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot has been happening for me and I don&amp;#39;t have much time for website updates. I still need to show off my new rice for Hyprland, even though I&amp;#39;m not in a graphical environment much anymore. That&amp;#39;s right! Let&amp;#39;s go Linux Console! Yeah I mean those &lt;code&gt;/dev/tty&lt;/code&gt; devices we all have on our GNU/Linux machines. I figured, as long as I am mostly in emacs and don&amp;#39;t need a graphical stack then that will work just fine and so I don&amp;#39;t spend much time in Hyprland these days. I mostly just use emacs as a sort of operating environment in the TTY and only start Hyprland if I need to do something like preview this site in a graphical browser. I even do a lot of web searches right in the TTY thanks to &lt;code&gt;ddgr&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;elinks&lt;/code&gt;. I do still have a new rice for Hyprland to show off though, and will, hopefully get it up soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
As for any other news, well, life goes on. Still just working and trying to make the most of my free time watching anime or playing video games. I actually used to be a pretty big fan of anime back in college, but that changed when life got busy, and I rarely watched a single new thing. I&amp;#39;m trying to change that though. I&amp;#39;ve gone back to some old shows and have managed to get my hands on a couple new ones. I do hope to spend a bit more time working on this website, but I won&amp;#39;t promise anything right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            </content>   
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/site" term="site" label="site" /> 
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/news" term="news" label="news" /> 
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/blog" term="blog" label="blog" />
        </entry>
        <entry>
            <title>Yuzu Is Dead</title>
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/post/yuzu-is-dead/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"  hreflang="en" />
            <id>http://onigirionegai.info/post/yuzu-is-dead/</id>
            <published>2024-03-06T19:37:27-08:00</published>
            <updated>2024-03-06T19:37:27-08:00</updated>
            <content type="html">
                
&lt;p&gt;
So, I like emulators. I don&amp;#39;t like emulators because they allow us to pirate games. I mean, I&amp;#39;m not going to sit here like some sort of self-righteous moron and tell you that emulators aren&amp;#39;t meant to be used that or, worse, that no one uses them that way, but that&amp;#39;s not the reason I think they should exist. Emulators are important because they help us preserve and play games that are no longer available. They also let us use hardware that was originally not designed to play games, which is cool, but could still be considered piracy. Either way, I think, when one is taken out, it harms the gaming industry and potential fans of beloved old franchises who will never get to play some games. Is this entirely true for emulators like Yuzu that emulate currently in-production hardware, perhaps not, but it can have lasting consequences for us when even these emulators are not protected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-1&#34;&gt;
What was Yuzu?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yuzu was a very popular Nintendo Switch emulator. All it did was emulate the unique hardware environment that exists inside the Nintendo Switch. On its own it doesn&amp;#39;t even provide the Switch&amp;#39;s firmware or operating system, just the hardware (in software form because emulators are weird). It is required that the user backs up their own Switch&amp;#39;s firmware and portions of its NAND flash memory in order for it to work correctly. This includes the Switch&amp;#39;s own encryption keys. I&amp;#39;m not a lawyer, so this is not legal advice, but bro-to-bro, this is probably the most legal way to create an emulator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-2&#34;&gt;
So What Happened?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frankly, Nintendo didn&amp;#39;t have the same view that I have. Now I did mention that Yuzu was extremely popular and, regardless of the intent of the developers, it was used to gain access to content that was not even out yet, like early builds of Tears of the Kingdom. Nintendo certainly didn&amp;#39;t like it so they filed a lawsuit against the developers. I do not know the amount of the lawsuit, but it was likely quite a lot for a company that was mostly supported by Patrons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Either fearing ballooning expenses for litigation or other items that Nintendo could have found out about during discovery, they decided not proceed to court. The Yuzu developers settled outside of court for 2.4 million USD! As part of this settlement they were required take down Yuzu and delete the code base. Hence, Yuzu is dead!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-3&#34;&gt;
And All the Pirates Cried!
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While that&amp;#39;s probably true, the pirates are not the only people who lose here. Here&amp;#39;s the thing. I&amp;#39;ll say it straight up for you! You wanna play a Nintendo Switch game, you should get a Nintendo Switch, but there are some people who legitimately can&amp;#39;t play games on the console. They may need special hardware to interface with the game or other accessibility options that the Nintendo Switch doesn&amp;#39;t support, but are available on PC and maybe there are just people who want to use a different controller or need higher frame-rates. Remember, when used as the developers intended, Yuzu wouldn&amp;#39;t cut out the need to own a Nintendo Switch, but would allow for others to play the games that they wouldn&amp;#39;t be able to play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Setting all of that aside, however, if we can. There are also other reasons we need to be careful about this. What happens when we can&amp;#39;t play the games as they are intended to be played any more. Eventually Nintendo will move on from its Switch console and stop making them. The console uses NAND flash chips and a battery which have a limited lifespan. This means there will come a time when we can&amp;#39;t play games on the Nintendo Switch. Think of how rare it is to find a working SNES or Sega Genesis. How are we able to play those games? Most of us use emulators. I know I do. What could happen is this will set a precedent that companies can sell us something prevent us from playing it, and then charge us again for the privilege of being able to play it in the future. This is bad for all of us. Good of Sony. Good for Nintendo. Bad for us. This is way the death of Yuzu is a bad thing for all gamers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-4&#34;&gt;
What Can be Done?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, nothing. Yuzu has already settled out of court, they have already pulled Yuzu and its code-base from the internet. The only thing left is for developers to not give up. We need to fork Yuzu and offer new versions. If Nintendo cuts one of us down we will simply return and in bigger numbers! For those, like me, who don&amp;#39;t have the knowledge to do this, we can support emulators and those that make them. Show Nintendo that they can&amp;#39;t sue everyone. Good news is, I have reason to believe that forks of Yuzu and/or other Nintendo Switch emulators have already been released so perhaps Nintendo won&amp;#39;t be able to win after all. We&amp;#39;ll just have to see how they respond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            </content>   
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/news" term="news" label="news" /> 
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/blog" term="blog" label="blog" />
        </entry>
        <entry>
            <title>Forums moving to GitHub Discussions</title>
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/post/forums-github/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"  hreflang="en" />
            <id>http://onigirionegai.info/post/forums-github/</id>
            <published>2023-11-16T12:26:36-08:00</published>
            <updated>2023-11-16T12:26:36-08:00</updated>
            <content type="html">
                
&lt;p&gt;
Over the past couple of years I have hosted a set of discussion forums on this server using phpBB. The idea was to give members of our community a way to discuss things with us and each other and generally just get together. Forums were also going to be away for patrons to access and discuss content and the direction of stories. We have had no adoption and it became a place where I could exchange ideas and private messages only with the other staff members and friends. While this is not a bad purpose, as this really doesn&amp;#39;t affect the server that much we have decided to shut these forums down. If anyone would like to discuss this site or our future plans, they can still do so, but will now require a GitHub account as we have simply set up GitHub Discussions for each repository associated with the server. The one for this site, for example, is located &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jjon-saxton/onigiri/discussions&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-1&#34;&gt;
Comments vs Discussions vs Issues
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While currently not enabled (I&amp;#39;m weighing options) on this site, we are looking to enable comments on each blog page to allow for some engagement. This is currently done on &lt;a href=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/&#34;&gt;Yayoi&amp;#39;s site&lt;/a&gt; using a GitHub project called utteranc.es. This allows people to post comments as issues in GitHub. The comments still appear on the page below the main content as they should for a blog, but she gets to review, reply, and manage them from her repo. While this seems awesome, it does require that everyone has a GitHub account, so I&amp;#39;m weighing other options for engagement. If we do establish comments those would be used for specific information on a page while discussions would be more for project discussion and general site comments. You can also raise issues on the GitHub repo if you notice problems. Yayoi uses her comment section for that as well because, as I mentioned, they use GitHub issues in the backend, but that may not be the best if we use something else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-2&#34;&gt;
Future of Community Engagement
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would still like to build a community here. Once I have a comment system in place I&amp;#39;m hoping everyone will use it. We are artists and we like showing our art. Its great to just create things, but would be so much better if we knew it was really appriciated. At the end of the day that&amp;#39;s what this is all about. Please engage with us on our GitHub discussions or even in the comment sections if/when they are available. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;headline-3&#34;&gt;
List of Discussions
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-3&#34;&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jjon-saxton/onigiri/discussions&#34;&gt;Onigiri☆Onegai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/yayoi-chi/yaya-world/discussions&#34;&gt;Yaya&amp;#39;s World&lt;/a&gt; (Don&amp;#39;t forget to hit up Yayoi in her comments too 😉)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            </content>   
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/site" term="site" label="site" /> 
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/news" term="news" label="news" />
        </entry>
        <entry>
            <title>&#34;Macs Can&#39;t Game&#34;</title>
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/post/mac-gaming/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"  hreflang="en" />
            <id>http://onigirionegai.info/post/mac-gaming/</id>
            <published>2023-09-27T18:40:52-07:00</published>
            <updated>2023-09-27T18:40:52-07:00</updated>
            <content type="html">
                
&lt;p&gt;
If you&amp;#39;re a user of a modern Mac, not a Macintosh or Apple computer, but a Mac, because that&amp;#39;s what we call them these days, then you have probably heard &lt;em&gt;someone&lt;/em&gt; say, but Jon (I&amp;#39;m using my name because I have heard this, but use your name instead) Macs can&amp;#39;t game, right? I mean its kind of the reputation the platform has especially today since, due to the fundamentally different architecture, we can&amp;#39;t just throw a copy of Windows on there and call it a day. The question is: Is this really true? To really answer this question we have to actually understand the statement. Let&amp;#39;s start there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-1&#34;&gt;
What do you mean &amp;#34;Macs Can&amp;#39;t Game&amp;#34;?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is really an over generalized statement and we first need to understand this before we can support or refute it. Here is what I mean. The statement assumes, like many things in life these days, a digital state. That is like newer digital TV signals you either have 100% or 0%. There are no states in between. Applying this to Mac gaming means that you either can play 100% of the games you own or you can&amp;#39;t play any games at all. However, this negates some of the actual accomplishments of the system and makes it sound as if you can&amp;#39;t play any games on a Mac. This is not true, and I don&amp;#39;t just mean Apple Arcade games, but lets talk about that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-2&#34;&gt;
Apple Arcade
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The above statement assumes no games run on Macs. It even negates Apple Arcade. Now, I will give many PC gamers a pass here. The type of games available on Apple Arcade are probably not the games they actually want to play. Because of the nature of Apple Arcade and requirements from Apple, all games released on Apple Arcade must support all platform that run the arcade software, this includes devices like the Apple TV and iPhone SE. Many Apple Arcade games, therefore, are phone games or very low quality games that you could just play on your phone, so what&amp;#39;s the point in playing them on a Mac and why even include them? Well, you see, they are still games and that means that Macs do have a large library of games they can play. As I said though, I&amp;#39;ll give you PC gamers a bit of a pass, but we should probably change the statement to reflect this &amp;#34;Macs can&amp;#39;t play the games I want to play.&amp;#34;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-3&#34;&gt;
AAA Titles
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only that also isn&amp;#39;t entirely accurate. I &lt;em&gt;could&lt;/em&gt; bust out my nerd game and say something to the effect of: Well, Intel Macs exist still an you could just use boot camp on one of those computers to install Windows and therefore there are a lot of Macs that can play whatever game you want, I don&amp;#39;t even need to go there. The very fact that Steam runs on Macs &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; allude to the fact that there are decent, non-Apple Arcade games, that actually run natively on even Apple Silicon M1/M2 Macs. Just one title that I noticed is &amp;#34;No Man&amp;#39;s Sky&amp;#34;. You can install and run that through Steam on macOS without issues. Is it the best experience out there? Probably not, certainly not on something like the 2020 M1 MacBook Air, but even that is just about as good as a Steam Deck. &amp;#34;No Man&amp;#39;s Sky&amp;#34; is also no the only game that runs on a Mac. Just a quick look at my own library shows the following AAA titles that I could install and run on a Mac:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BioShock/BioShock 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deues Ex: Mankind Divided&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Middle Earth: Shadow of Mordor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rise of the Tomb Raider&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shadow of the Tomb Raider&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tomb Raider&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No Man&amp;#39;s Sky&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is that a really long list? No, not by a long shot, but seven games is more than none. Are these games all that new? Also no, but then again I don&amp;#39;t have very many new titles in my own library to look at. The point is that there &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; games that you can play on a Mac so saying Macs can&amp;#39;t game is not exactly accurate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-4&#34;&gt;
Does the really matter?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The harsh reality is of the 202 titles in my library (that&amp;#39;s all titles), only 30 will run on the Mac. Also, I don&amp;#39;t play many of the 30 games that would run. &amp;#34;No Man&amp;#39;s Sky&amp;#34; is the only game I have played extensively on the Mac, but that does mean I have played a game on the Mac and, in fact, I have also played non-steam games including &amp;#34;The Sims 4&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;StarCraft II&amp;#34;, and &amp;#34;Fantasian&amp;#34; (one of which is a very good Apple Arcade title). So I&amp;#39;m not only capable of playing games on the Mac, but I have actually done so. Is it my platform of choice for gaming? No. I wouldn&amp;#39;t even use it for productivity. I know at least one person who would use a Mac over a PC (even running Linux), but not for running games. That being said, the statement isn&amp;#39;t about preference it is about capability. Macs are capable of running games therefore to say they can&amp;#39;t is just wrong. However, what can it hurt to just say they can&amp;#39;t play games? After all they certainly don&amp;#39;t play many so its not entirely incorrect and maybe it will better prepare people for when they are trying to decide on that one laptop for school or work. Well, there are actually problems with a blanket label like that:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It breads an attitude in consumers that they should not buy a Mac if gaming is something they want to use it for at all&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It makes the Mac look like a platform that should not be targeted as platform to release games on&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This could effect efforts of those who are considering releasing games for the Mac and result in a sort of chicken and egg problem. There are no games for the Mac, so no one buy a Mac for gaming, therefore there is no interest in developing games for the Mac, therefore the are no games for the Mac. If we at least acknowledge the Mac&amp;#39;s potential as a platform for games then perhaps we can break that cycle. Unfortunately, that is up to us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-5&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-5&#34;&gt;
What next?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-5&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my next blog post I will be comparing the Mac and the Steam Deck as gaming platforms. Both of these devices are not typically targeted as release platforms for large PC games, but one plays many more games then the other. I&amp;#39;ll discuss why and why it matters. I&amp;#39;ll also bring up the GamePorting ToolKit from Apple and how it is different from Valve&amp;#39;s efforts. I&amp;#39;ll even explain why it likely won&amp;#39;t help the Mac. Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            </content>   
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/news" term="news" label="news" /> 
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/blog" term="blog" label="blog" />
        </entry>
        <entry>
            <title>Site Look</title>
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/post/site-look/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"  hreflang="en" />
            <id>http://onigirionegai.info/post/site-look/</id>
            <published>2023-09-14T12:47:20-07:00</published>
            <updated>2023-09-14T12:47:20-07:00</updated>
            <content type="html">
                &lt;p&gt;
It has been a couple of weeks now since I have changed the purpose of this site. With this change came a new look. To be honest the look was chosen for two reasons and neither are particularly good:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It looked pretty good&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It seemed pretty easy to install&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I&amp;#39;m being even more honest I would say the second reason is the biggest factor. Which is related to how, unfortunately, lazy I&amp;#39;ve come when it comes to this site. I fully recognize that the original site had a lot more…we&amp;#39;ll call it…personality. To me it just had a look to it that screamed anime or visual novel without looking too much like a Japanese site. It struck a good balance between the type of content we provided and the origin of our group, that being the United States. This site does look fairly professional, but it lacks some of the charm of the old one. I understand this. The problem is, is there a problem? What I mean is, is it bad that we lost that charm? Maybe its better without it? That&amp;#39;s where I need your opinion. I have a &lt;a href=&#34;https://forums.onigirionegai.info/viewtopic.php?t=28&#34;&gt;forum post&lt;/a&gt; up with a poll and would like anyone to tell me what they think. Should we try to get that personality back, or is this better?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
While I would love to tell you that I have more news, it has been a bit slow on that front today. I am looking at other sites and pages to showcase though. I&amp;#39;ve been catching up on anime and trying to help some friends, so I haven&amp;#39;t had as much time to go through some of the suggestions. I&amp;#39;ll have something up for next week though. Right now, let&amp;#39;s enjoy the break :smile:&lt;/p&gt;

            </content>   
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/news" term="news" label="news" /> 
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/site" term="site" label="site" />
        </entry>
        <entry>
            <title>Site Showcase: 03 Sep 2023</title>
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/post/showcase/03Sep2023/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"  hreflang="en" />
            <id>http://onigirionegai.info/post/showcase/03Sep2023/</id>
            <published>2023-09-03T12:10:10-07:00</published>
            <updated>2023-09-03T12:10:10-07:00</updated>
            <content type="html">
                &lt;p&gt;
Welcome to the inaugural episode of the very well titled and not completely stupidly named segment known as the &amp;#34;Site Showcase&amp;#34;! In this short post I will talk pick one post or article from one of our member sites to talk about. I mean we want their sites to be more discoverable, what better way to do that than to make showcase something I thought was cool about their site this week!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Without further ado, let&amp;#39;s talk about Yayoi! Well, more specifically, we&amp;#39;ll talk about &lt;a href=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/commissions/&#34;&gt;this post&lt;/a&gt;! While it would be easy, given how new this particular site is, to pick something here, I really want to showcase other members and Yayoi is looking for people to commission her! The post goes over the type of things that she is good at and the type of things she won&amp;#39;t touch as well as how you can commission her. Of course she is a bit humble and doesn&amp;#39;t really mention that she is actually a very good artists and you should really consider her if you need something drawn. I&amp;#39;ve known her for a bit and she actually did the old banner for the original site. I may even commission her to do a new one for this version of the site. Of course I can endorse her all I want, but I don&amp;#39;t know if that really shows you how good of an artist she is. So, I think I&amp;#39;ll show you. Here are a few samples of recent works from her &lt;a href=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/&#34;&gt;gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/I%27llNeverLetGo.png&#34; alt=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/I%27llNeverLetGo.png&#34; title=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/I%27llNeverLetGo.png&#34; width=&#34;34%&#34; align=&#34;left&#34;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/KotatsuKurisumasu.png&#34; alt=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/KotatsuKurisumasu.png&#34; title=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/KotatsuKurisumasu.png&#34; width=&#34;33%&#34; align=&#34;left&#34;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/IwasThere.png&#34; alt=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/IwasThere.png&#34; title=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/IwasThere.png&#34; width=&#34;33%&#34; align=&#34;left&#34;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Anyway, I hope you give her a change. Check out the original post on her &lt;a href=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/commissions/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; for more information on how to commission her. Also check out our &lt;a href=&#34;https://forums.onigirionegai.info&#34;&gt;forums&lt;/a&gt; if you would like to discuss this showcase or suggests other things you would like us to cover!&lt;/p&gt;

            </content>   
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/site" term="site" label="site" /> 
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/news" term="news" label="news" />
        </entry>
</feed>
