<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <generator uri="https://gohugo.io/" version="0.116.1">Hugo</generator>
    <title>Onigiri☆Onegai</title>
            <link href="http://localhost/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="html" />
            <link href="http://localhost/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" title="Atom" />
    <updated>2023-09-03T21:02:55-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://localhost/</id>
        <entry>
            <title>About Onigiri☆Onegai</title>
            <link href="http://localhost/post/about/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"  hreflang="en" />
            <id>http://localhost/post/about/</id>
            <published>2023-09-01T20:49:27-07:00</published>
            <updated>2023-09-01T20:49:27-07:00</updated>
            <content type="html">
                
&lt;p&gt;
In short Onigiri☆Onegai is a group of creative individuals. Our mission is to bring our dreams alive, whatever they may be, using the talents available to us. Whether that means writing great stories, drawing awesome pictures, or creating mods for our favorite video games. It could even mean building websites or awesome rices! That&amp;#39;s right, at least one of us is a Linux user. That one, may, or may not, be the one who is writing this page right now 😉!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-1&#34;&gt;
Who are we?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently there are three users. Each one has a separate site which focus on different things. The sites are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://onigirionegai.info/~miu&#34;&gt;http://onigirionegai.info/~miu&lt;/a&gt;, which focuses on mods and CC for the Sims 4&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi&#34;&gt;http://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi&lt;/a&gt;, which focuses mostly on video games and art.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://onigirionegai.info/&#34;&gt;http://onigirionegai.info/&lt;/a&gt;, this site which once focused on creating javascript-based visual novels, but now focuses on information and GNU/Linux rices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-2&#34;&gt;
Can you join?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In short, yes! Actually the best way to get started is to join our &lt;a href=&#34;http://fourms.onigirionegai.info&#34;&gt;http://fourms.onigirionegai.info&lt;/a&gt;. There you can start talking about your interests and let us know how you would like to contribute, or if there is any projects you think we could help you with. If any of us think your project is something we could contribute to, or if we think you can help us with our projects, then we&amp;#39;ll add you as a contributor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-3&#34;&gt;
What are we working on?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now, each of us has our own projects. We were coming together for the aforementioned VNs, but, sadly, we are too busy and too small to work one those. That isn&amp;#39;t to say we don&amp;#39;t plan on releasing them in the future, but we are looking at additional options. We still come together to help out, but, if you want to know what each of us are working on, it is best to check out the different sites linked above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-4&#34;&gt;
Any plans for the future?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are! We are weighing our options and trying to decide how we can best work together. We&amp;#39;ll also be looking for additional contributors and collaborators who have ideas on how to best help us move forward. Right now, we all fairly busy though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-5&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-5&#34;&gt;
Are there any other ways to contribute?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-5&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are not particularly good at programming, or art, or, like us, don&amp;#39;t have much time, there is another way to contribute. We would like to be able to focus more on our projects. To do this we will need to, unfortunately, be able to take care of needs &lt;em&gt;without&lt;/em&gt; full-time jobs. At the moment we do have a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?u=29802411&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fonigirionegai.info%2F&amp;amp;utm_medium=widget&#34;&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt; available. It will get you access to pre-release content and special areas of the forums. We hope to expend perks as we are able to as well. We thank you for your support! Also, if Patreon doesn&amp;#39;t seem like a good fit for you, at least one of us takes &lt;a href=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/commissions/&#34;&gt;commissions&lt;/a&gt;, this will still be a great support to her and to the group!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            </content>   
                                <category scheme="http://localhost/tags/about" term="about" label="about" />
        </entry>
        <entry>
            <title>Site Showcase: 03 Sep 2023</title>
            <link href="http://localhost/post/showcase/03Sep2023/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"  hreflang="en" />
            <id>http://localhost/post/showcase/03Sep2023/</id>
            <published>2023-09-03T12:10:10-07:00</published>
            <updated>2023-09-03T12:10:10-07:00</updated>
            <content type="html">
                &lt;p&gt;
Welcome to the inaugural episode of the very well titled and not completely stupidly named segment known as the &amp;#34;Site Showcase&amp;#34;! In this short post I will talk pick one post or article from one of our member sites to talk about. I mean we want their sites to be more discoverable, what better way to do that than to make showcase something I thought was cool about their site this week!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Without further ado, let&amp;#39;s talk about Yayoi! Well, more specifically, we&amp;#39;ll talk about &lt;a href=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/commissions/&#34;&gt;this post&lt;/a&gt;! While it would be easy, given how new this particular site is, to pick something here, I really want to showcase other members and Yayoi is looking for people to commission her! The post goes over the type of things that she is good at and the type of things she won&amp;#39;t touch as well as how you can commission her. Of course she is a bit humble and doesn&amp;#39;t really mention that she is actually a very good artists and you should really consider her if you need something drawn. I&amp;#39;ve known her for a bit and she actually did the old banner for the original site. I may even commission her to do a new one for this version of the site. Of course I can endorse her all I want, but I don&amp;#39;t know if that really shows you how good of an artist she is. So, I think I&amp;#39;ll show you. Here are a few samples of recent works from her &lt;a href=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/&#34;&gt;gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/I%27llNeverLetGo.png&#34; alt=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/I%27llNeverLetGo.png&#34; title=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/I%27llNeverLetGo.png&#34; width=&#34;34%&#34; align=&#34;left&#34;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/KotatsuKurisumasu.png&#34; alt=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/KotatsuKurisumasu.png&#34; title=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/KotatsuKurisumasu.png&#34; width=&#34;33%&#34; align=&#34;left&#34;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/IwasThere.png&#34; alt=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/IwasThere.png&#34; title=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/IwasThere.png&#34; width=&#34;33%&#34; align=&#34;left&#34;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Anyway, I hope you give her a change. Check out the original post on her &lt;a href=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/commissions/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; for more information on how to commission her. Also check out our &lt;a href=&#34;https://forums.onigirionegai.info&#34;&gt;forums&lt;/a&gt; if you would like to discuss this showcase or suggests other things you would like us to cover!&lt;/p&gt;

            </content>   
                                <category scheme="http://localhost/tags/site" term="site" label="site" /> 
                                <category scheme="http://localhost/tags/news" term="news" label="news" />
        </entry>
        <entry>
            <title>We are making some changes!</title>
            <link href="http://localhost/post/changes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"  hreflang="en" />
            <id>http://localhost/post/changes/</id>
            <published>2023-09-03T11:40:20-07:00</published>
            <updated>2023-09-03T11:40:20-07:00</updated>
            <content type="html">
                
&lt;p&gt;
As you have no doubt noticed, the site is different than it was before. We are moving this site to more of a blog-style format. This is being done for a few reasons:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We no longer have the time to work on large projects and many of those of languished without recent updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We believe the root domain, &lt;a href=&#34;http://onigirionegai.info&#34;&gt;onigirionegai.info&lt;/a&gt; should focus on information on the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We each have our own websites now as well and would like those to be more discoverable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If we do work on other large projects, we would like them to have separate websites with their own style and theme rather than just be part of a larger &amp;#34;root&amp;#34; site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me explain each of these in a bit more detail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-1&#34;&gt;
We no longer have the time…
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sadly we have all become much busier as our lives have moved on and we are not able to provide the time and attention we once dreamt of when we came together. Rather than deciding to close the site, however, I decided to leave it open. It will now serve as a launchpad of discovery. I will blog about my own small projects and about the state of my collaborator&amp;#39;s projects. They may be smaller, but we are not just sitting on our hands. We simply need to be able to live and the types of large projects that cannot provide income at the moment are not things we can focus too much time on. We hope, that, in the future, we will be able to come together again. I talk a little about this on the &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost/post/about/&#34;&gt;about page&lt;/a&gt; and will elaborate further a little later. Please have patience with us and don&amp;#39;t forget to check out our other sites!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-2&#34;&gt;
The domain is .info, should it should be information-focused, right?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I won&amp;#39;t say too much here, but this was a factor. The previous site was a little too unfocused and general. I think, being that this is a .info domain, at least the root site should be more information-focused. Now I won&amp;#39;t go so far as to tell my collaborators how they should run their sites, or the type of content they should have even if their URL is still attached to this one. I just think &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; site should be more focused on providing information, organization news, site news, and announcements, than on the projects themselves. This also leads into the last point, but first!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-3&#34;&gt;
We each have our own websites and would like those to be more discoverable
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One look at the home page and you&amp;#39;ll find a pinned post, this is the aforementioned &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost/post/about/&#34;&gt;about page&lt;/a&gt;. That page lists the sites that each of us now work on. Within a couple of clicks we now have a list of sub-sites. These were not even mentioned previously. It was up to each member to promote their personal sites even if they were hosted here. This is now no longer the case. So be sure to check them out! Now onto that last point that I mentioned just one paragraph ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-4&#34;&gt;
We want websites for each project not one &amp;#34;one-size-fits-none&amp;#34; site
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the original idea of this site as a means of both introducing ourselves and our projects was not a bad one, it wasn&amp;#39;t the best. One over-arching site is just too big and any future projects we do come together for would simply be lost in a sea of other projects, especially if those projects are many and all large. Therefore, each project will have its own dedicated site that will be designed for its own identity. This, of course is something that will happen later. I mentioned we would &lt;em&gt;like&lt;/em&gt; to work on larger projects, but that is not possible at this time. If you would like to help though, I have information on how that could be possible on the &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost/post/about/&#34;&gt;most link page ever&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            </content>   
                                <category scheme="http://localhost/tags/announcements" term="announcements" label="announcements" /> 
                                <category scheme="http://localhost/tags/site" term="site" label="site" />
        </entry>
</feed>
