<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <generator uri="https://gohugo.io/" version="0.118.2">Hugo</generator>
    <title>Onigiri☆Onegai</title>
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="html" />
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" title="Atom" />
    <updated>2023-10-02T16:06:35-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://onigirionegai.info/</id>
        <entry>
            <title>About Onigiri☆Onegai</title>
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/post/about/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"  hreflang="en" />
            <id>http://onigirionegai.info/post/about/</id>
            <published>2023-09-01T20:49:27-07:00</published>
            <updated>2023-09-01T20:49:27-07:00</updated>
            <content type="html">
                
&lt;p&gt;
In short Onigiri☆Onegai is a group of creative individuals. Our mission is to bring our dreams alive, whatever they may be, using the talents available to us. Whether that means writing great stories, drawing awesome pictures, or creating mods for our favorite video games. It could even mean building websites or awesome rices! That&amp;#39;s right, at least one of us is a Linux user. That one, may, or may not, be the one who is writing this page right now 😉!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-1&#34;&gt;
Who are we?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently there are three users. Each one has a separate site which focus on different things. The sites are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/vue.min.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;ul id=&#34;OOProjects&#34;&gt;
	&lt;li v-if=&#34;project.url &amp;&amp; !project.private&#34; v-for=&#34;project in list&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a :href=&#34;project.url&#34;&gt;{{project.title}}&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;project-repo&#34; v-if=&#34;project.git&#34;&gt;&lt;a :href=&#34;project.git&#34;&gt;Git Repo: {{project.git}}&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;project-desc&#34; v-if=&#34;project.description&#34;&gt;{{project.description}}&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
	var app= new Vue({
			el: &#39;#OOProjects&#39;,
			data:{
					list: []
				},
			created(){
					fetch(&#39;https://onigirionegai.info/projects.php&#39;)
						.then(response =&gt; response.json())
						.then (json=&gt; {
								this.list = json
							})
				}
		});
&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-2&#34;&gt;
Can you join?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In short, yes! Actually the best way to get started is to join our &lt;a href=&#34;https://forums.onigirionegai.info&#34;&gt;forums&lt;/a&gt;. There you can start talking about your interests and let us know how you would like to contribute, or if there is any projects you think we could help you with. If any of us think your project is something we could contribute to, or if we think you can help us with our projects, then we&amp;#39;ll add you as a contributor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-3&#34;&gt;
What are we working on?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now, each of us has our own projects. We were coming together for the aforementioned VNs, but, sadly, we are too busy and too small to work one those. That isn&amp;#39;t to say we don&amp;#39;t plan on releasing them in the future, but we are looking at additional options. We still come together to help out, but, if you want to know what each of us are working on, it is best to check out the different sites linked above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-4&#34;&gt;
Any plans for the future?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are! We are weighing our options and trying to decide how we can best work together. We&amp;#39;ll also be looking for additional contributors and collaborators who have ideas on how to best help us move forward. Right now, we all fairly busy though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-5&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-5&#34;&gt;
Are there any other ways to contribute?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-5&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are not particularly good at programming, or art, or, like us, don&amp;#39;t have much time, there is another way to contribute. We would like to be able to focus more on our projects. To do this we will need to, unfortunately, be able to take care of needs &lt;em&gt;without&lt;/em&gt; full-time jobs. At the moment we do have a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?u=29802411&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fonigirionegai.info%2F&amp;amp;utm_medium=widget&#34;&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt; available. It will get you access to pre-release content and special areas of the forums. We hope to expend perks as we are able to as well. We thank you for your support! Also, if Patreon doesn&amp;#39;t seem like a good fit for you, at least one of us takes &lt;a href=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/commissions/&#34;&gt;commissions&lt;/a&gt;, this will still be a great support to her and to the group!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            </content>   
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/about" term="about" label="about" />
        </entry>
        <entry>
            <title>&#34;Macs Can&#39;t Game&#34;</title>
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/post/mac-gaming/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"  hreflang="en" />
            <id>http://onigirionegai.info/post/mac-gaming/</id>
            <published>2023-09-27T18:40:52-07:00</published>
            <updated>2023-09-27T18:40:52-07:00</updated>
            <content type="html">
                
&lt;p&gt;
If you&amp;#39;re a user of a modern Mac, not a Macintosh or Apple computer, but a Mac, because that&amp;#39;s what we call them these days, then you have probably heard &lt;em&gt;someone&lt;/em&gt; say, but Jon (I&amp;#39;m using my name because I have heard this, but use your name instead) Macs can&amp;#39;t game, right? I mean its kind of the reputation the platform has especially today since, due to the fundamentally different architecture, we can&amp;#39;t just throw a copy of Windows on there and call it a day. The question is: Is this really true? To really answer this question we have to actually understand the statement. Let&amp;#39;s start there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-1&#34;&gt;
What do you mean &amp;#34;Macs Can&amp;#39;t Game&amp;#34;?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is really an over generalized statement and we first need to understand this before we can support or refute it. Here is what I mean. The statement assumes, like many things in life these days, a digital state. That is like newer digital TV signals you either have 100% or 0%. There are no states in between. Applying this to Mac gaming means that you either can play 100% of the games you own or you can&amp;#39;t play any games at all. However, this negates some of the actual accomplishments of the system and makes it sound as if you can&amp;#39;t play any games on a Mac. This is not true, and I don&amp;#39;t just mean Apple Arcade games, but lets talk about that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-2&#34;&gt;
Apple Arcade
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The above statement assumes no games run on Macs. It even negates Apple Arcade. Now, I will give many PC gamers a pass here. The type of games available on Apple Arcade are probably not the games they actually want to play. Because of the nature of Apple Arcade and requirements from Apple, all games released on Apple Arcade must support all platform that run the arcade software, this includes devices like the Apple TV and iPhone SE. Many Apple Arcade games, therefore, are phone games or very low quality games that you could just play on your phone, so what&amp;#39;s the point in playing them on a Mac and why even include them? Well, you see, they are still games and that means that Macs do have a large library of games they can play. As I said though, I&amp;#39;ll give you PC gamers a bit of a pass, but we should probably change the statement to reflect this &amp;#34;Macs can&amp;#39;t play the games I want to play.&amp;#34;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-3&#34;&gt;
AAA Titles
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only that also isn&amp;#39;t entirely accurate. I &lt;em&gt;could&lt;/em&gt; bust out my nerd game and say something to the effect of: Well, Intel Macs exist still an you could just use boot camp on one of those computers to install Windows and therefore there are a lot of Macs that can play whatever game you want, I don&amp;#39;t even need to go there. The very fact that Steam runs on Macs &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; allude to the fact that there are decent, non-Apple Arcade games, that actually run natively on even Apple Silicon M1/M2 Macs. Just one title that I noticed is &amp;#34;No Man&amp;#39;s Sky&amp;#34;. You can install and run that through Steam on macOS without issues. Is it the best experience out there? Probably not, certainly not on something like the 2020 M1 MacBook Air, but even that is just about as good as a Steam Deck. &amp;#34;No Man&amp;#39;s Sky&amp;#34; is also no the only game that runs on a Mac. Just a quick look at my own library shows the following AAA titles that I could install and run on a Mac:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BioShock/BioShock 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deues Ex: Mankind Divided&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Middle Earth: Shadow of Mordor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rise of the Tomb Raider&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shadow of the Tomb Raider&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tomb Raider&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No Man&amp;#39;s Sky&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is that a really long list? No, not by a long shot, but seven games is more than none. Are these games all that new? Also no, but then again I don&amp;#39;t have very many new titles in my own library to look at. The point is that there &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; games that you can play on a Mac so saying Macs can&amp;#39;t game is not exactly accurate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-4&#34;&gt;
Does the really matter?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The harsh reality is of the 202 titles in my library (that&amp;#39;s all titles), only 30 will run on the Mac. Also, I don&amp;#39;t play many of the 30 games that would run. &amp;#34;No Man&amp;#39;s Sky&amp;#34; is the only game I have played extensively on the Mac, but that does mean I have played a game on the Mac and, in fact, I have also played non-steam games including &amp;#34;The Sims 4&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;StarCraft II&amp;#34;, and &amp;#34;Fantasian&amp;#34; (one of which is a very good Apple Arcade title). So I&amp;#39;m not only capable of playing games on the Mac, but I have actually done so. Is it my platform of choice for gaming? No. I wouldn&amp;#39;t even use it for productivity. I know at least one person who would use a Mac over a PC (even running Linux), but not for running games. That being said, the statement isn&amp;#39;t about preference it is about capability. Macs are capable of running games therefore to say they can&amp;#39;t is just wrong. However, what can it hurt to just say they can&amp;#39;t play games? After all they certainly don&amp;#39;t play many so its not entirely incorrect and maybe it will better prepare people for when they are trying to decide on that one laptop for school or work. Well, there are actually problems with a blanket label like that:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It breads an attitude in consumers that they should not buy a Mac if gaming is something they want to use it for at all&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It makes the Mac look like a platform that should not be targeted as platform to release games on&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This could effect efforts of those who are considering releasing games for the Mac and result in a sort of chicken and egg problem. There are no games for the Mac, so no one buy a Mac for gaming, therefore there is no interest in developing games for the Mac, therefore the are no games for the Mac. If we at least acknowledge the Mac&amp;#39;s potential as a platform for games then perhaps we can break that cycle. Unfortunately, that is up to us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-5&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-5&#34;&gt;
What next?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-5&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my next blog post I will be comparing the Mac and the Steam Deck as gaming platforms. Both of these devices are not typically targeted as release platforms for large PC games, but one plays many more games then the other. I&amp;#39;ll discuss why and why it matters. I&amp;#39;ll also bring up the GamePorting ToolKit from Apple and how it is different from Valve&amp;#39;s efforts. I&amp;#39;ll even explain why it likely won&amp;#39;t help the Mac. Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            </content>   
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/news" term="news" label="news" /> 
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/blog" term="blog" label="blog" />
        </entry>
        <entry>
            <title>Site Look</title>
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/post/site-look/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"  hreflang="en" />
            <id>http://onigirionegai.info/post/site-look/</id>
            <published>2023-09-14T12:47:20-07:00</published>
            <updated>2023-09-14T12:47:20-07:00</updated>
            <content type="html">
                &lt;p&gt;
It has been a couple of weeks now since I have changed the purpose of this site. With this change came a new look. To be honest the look was chosen for two reasons and neither are particularly good:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It looked pretty good&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It seemed pretty easy to install&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I&amp;#39;m being even more honest I would say the second reason is the biggest factor. Which is related to how, unfortunately, lazy I&amp;#39;ve come when it comes to this site. I fully recognize that the original site had a lot more…we&amp;#39;ll call it…personality. To me it just had a look to it that screamed anime or visual novel without looking too much like a Japanese site. It struck a good balance between the type of content we provided and the origin of our group, that being the United States. This site does look fairly professional, but it lacks some of the charm of the old one. I understand this. The problem is, is there a problem? What I mean is, is it bad that we lost that charm? Maybe its better without it? That&amp;#39;s where I need your opinion. I have a &lt;a href=&#34;https://forums.onigirionegai.info/viewtopic.php?t=28&#34;&gt;forum post&lt;/a&gt; up with a poll and would like anyone to tell me what they think. Should we try to get that personality back, or is this better?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
While I would love to tell you that I have more news, it has been a bit slow on that front today. I am looking at other sites and pages to showcase though. I&amp;#39;ve been catching up on anime and trying to help some friends, so I haven&amp;#39;t had as much time to go through some of the suggestions. I&amp;#39;ll have something up for next week though. Right now, let&amp;#39;s enjoy the break 😄&lt;/p&gt;

            </content>   
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/news" term="news" label="news" /> 
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/site" term="site" label="site" />
        </entry>
        <entry>
            <title>Hyprland, Waybar, and a little Dracula</title>
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/post/hyprland-waybar/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"  hreflang="en" />
            <id>http://onigirionegai.info/post/hyprland-waybar/</id>
            <published>2023-09-05T16:26:34-07:00</published>
            <updated>2023-09-05T16:26:34-07:00</updated>
            <content type="html">
                
&lt;img src=&#34;/hyprland-waybar-clean.png&#34; alt=&#34;the clean waybar look&#34; title=&#34;/hyprland-waybar-clean.png&#34; width=&#34;90%&#34;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Halloween is coming! Okay, well Halloween is actually still pretty far away, but it happens to be my favorite holiday so, I guess I&amp;#39;m starting a little early. So, other than that little confession I have a few others:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I love the &lt;a href=&#34;https://draculatheme.com/contribute#color-palette&#34;&gt;Dracula Color Scheme&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been a bit obsessed with making a pill-based top status bar for a bit too long (wait until you see my Qtile config).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wayland might not be for everyone at the moment, but I love it because of Hyprland!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My current Waybar configuration, pictured above (along with a Halloween wallpaper I found) is something I am quite proud of, but aside from that, I like my entire Hyprland look and configuration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-1&#34;&gt;
Hyprland and Waybar
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p width=&#34;90%&#34; alt=&#34;hyprland and waybar together&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/hyprland-waybar.png&#34; alt=&#34;/hyprland-waybar.png&#34; title=&#34;/hyprland-waybar.png&#34;/&gt;
As you can see the purple from the Dracula color scheme seeps into the highlight borders of the active window while inactive windows retain a solid dark gray color that is often used for Dracula&amp;#39;s background. Also both Emacs and Kitty are configured for transparency so I can see my wallpaper behind them. In fact, I use mostly Qt apps and Kvantum is also configured for transparency, you just can&amp;#39;t see it very well in qutebrowser because it draws its own UI elements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Waybar is configured to show the current window, but you don&amp;#39;t see that section in the clean shot above. That&amp;#39;s because I hide it when its empty. The other sections are split and pill-shaped. I tried using multiple panels in KDE to do a similar effect once, but it didn&amp;#39;t come out quite as nicely as the above. Anyway I like how it all turned out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-2&#34;&gt;
Working with Waybar
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actually working with Waybar was pretty nice for me. I am somewhat familiar with JSON. The main configuration is a JSON file, so I felt right at home setting up the layout and widgets. Now, unlike Qtile, where all the configuration is in one file, Waybar separates the style and layout into separate files. Fortunately the style is all handled by CSS, which is something else I&amp;#39;m very familiar with, it just meant I had three files to edit and maintain instead of just two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-3&#34;&gt;
Working with Hyprland
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you might be able to infer, Hyprland did not come with a bar. This is different from Qtile which not only comes with a bar, but also several built-in widgets and even more distributed as part of the qtile-extras. Of course I heard about Waybar and that provides the bar, but it meant that configuration for the bar is separate, once again, from configuration for the compositor.
Additionally, I didn&amp;#39;t have much trouble editing the configuration file. It syntax is something that is at least a bit familiar, seems to be ini-like, and I had a few examples to pull from. It was really just a matter of finding the color portions for a Dracula example configuration and then finding and editing the keybindings. I did add window resize keybindings, but that turned out to be pretty easy after reading the &lt;a href=&#34;https://wiki.hyprland.org/&#34;&gt;Hyprland wiki&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-4&#34;&gt;
Github
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My configuration files are available on Github. If you would like to replicate this look on your own, you can just clone &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jjon-saxton/rice&#34;&gt;my repo&lt;/a&gt;. A note: swaybg and swaylock are required to use the configuration as it is written, wofi too. You may need my wofi-scripts as well, but I will be providing those in the future in a separate repo. If you don&amp;#39;t want to use those programs or tools, it should be fairly simple to switch them out for equivalents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            </content>   
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/rice" term="rice" label="rice" />
        </entry>
        <entry>
            <title>Site Showcase: 03 Sep 2023</title>
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/post/showcase/03Sep2023/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"  hreflang="en" />
            <id>http://onigirionegai.info/post/showcase/03Sep2023/</id>
            <published>2023-09-03T12:10:10-07:00</published>
            <updated>2023-09-03T12:10:10-07:00</updated>
            <content type="html">
                &lt;p&gt;
Welcome to the inaugural episode of the very well titled and not completely stupidly named segment known as the &amp;#34;Site Showcase&amp;#34;! In this short post I will talk pick one post or article from one of our member sites to talk about. I mean we want their sites to be more discoverable, what better way to do that than to make showcase something I thought was cool about their site this week!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Without further ado, let&amp;#39;s talk about Yayoi! Well, more specifically, we&amp;#39;ll talk about &lt;a href=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/commissions/&#34;&gt;this post&lt;/a&gt;! While it would be easy, given how new this particular site is, to pick something here, I really want to showcase other members and Yayoi is looking for people to commission her! The post goes over the type of things that she is good at and the type of things she won&amp;#39;t touch as well as how you can commission her. Of course she is a bit humble and doesn&amp;#39;t really mention that she is actually a very good artists and you should really consider her if you need something drawn. I&amp;#39;ve known her for a bit and she actually did the old banner for the original site. I may even commission her to do a new one for this version of the site. Of course I can endorse her all I want, but I don&amp;#39;t know if that really shows you how good of an artist she is. So, I think I&amp;#39;ll show you. Here are a few samples of recent works from her &lt;a href=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/&#34;&gt;gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/I%27llNeverLetGo.png&#34; alt=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/I%27llNeverLetGo.png&#34; title=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/I%27llNeverLetGo.png&#34; width=&#34;34%&#34; align=&#34;left&#34;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/KotatsuKurisumasu.png&#34; alt=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/KotatsuKurisumasu.png&#34; title=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/KotatsuKurisumasu.png&#34; width=&#34;33%&#34; align=&#34;left&#34;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/IwasThere.png&#34; alt=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/IwasThere.png&#34; title=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/creations/IwasThere.png&#34; width=&#34;33%&#34; align=&#34;left&#34;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Anyway, I hope you give her a change. Check out the original post on her &lt;a href=&#34;https://onigirionegai.info/~yayoi/gallery/commissions/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; for more information on how to commission her. Also check out our &lt;a href=&#34;https://forums.onigirionegai.info&#34;&gt;forums&lt;/a&gt; if you would like to discuss this showcase or suggests other things you would like us to cover!&lt;/p&gt;

            </content>   
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/site" term="site" label="site" /> 
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/news" term="news" label="news" />
        </entry>
        <entry>
            <title>We are making some changes!</title>
            <link href="http://onigirionegai.info/post/changes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"  hreflang="en" />
            <id>http://onigirionegai.info/post/changes/</id>
            <published>2023-09-03T11:40:20-07:00</published>
            <updated>2023-09-03T11:40:20-07:00</updated>
            <content type="html">
                
&lt;p&gt;
As you have no doubt noticed, the site is different than it was before. We are moving this site to more of a blog-style format. This is being done for a few reasons:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We no longer have the time to work on large projects and many of those of languished without recent updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We believe the root domain, &lt;a href=&#34;http://onigirionegai.info&#34;&gt;onigirionegai.info&lt;/a&gt; should focus on information on the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We each have our own websites now as well and would like those to be more discoverable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If we do work on other large projects, we would like them to have separate websites with their own style and theme rather than just be part of a larger &amp;#34;root&amp;#34; site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me explain each of these in a bit more detail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-1&#34;&gt;
We no longer have the time…
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-1&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sadly we have all become much busier as our lives have moved on and we are not able to provide the time and attention we once dreamt of when we came together. Rather than deciding to close the site, however, I decided to leave it open. It will now serve as a launchpad of discovery. I will blog about my own small projects and about the state of my collaborator&amp;#39;s projects. They may be smaller, but we are not just sitting on our hands. We simply need to be able to live and the types of large projects that cannot provide income at the moment are not things we can focus too much time on. We hope, that, in the future, we will be able to come together again. I talk a little about this on the &lt;a href=&#34;http://onigirionegai.info/post/about/&#34;&gt;about page&lt;/a&gt; and will elaborate further a little later. Please have patience with us and don&amp;#39;t forget to check out our other sites!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-2&#34;&gt;
The domain is .info, should it should be information-focused, right?
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-2&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I won&amp;#39;t say too much here, but this was a factor. The previous site was a little too unfocused and general. I think, being that this is a .info domain, at least the root site should be more information-focused. Now I won&amp;#39;t go so far as to tell my collaborators how they should run their sites, or the type of content they should have even if their URL is still attached to this one. I just think &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; site should be more focused on providing information, organization news, site news, and announcements, than on the projects themselves. This also leads into the last point, but first!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-3&#34;&gt;
We each have our own websites and would like those to be more discoverable
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-3&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One look at the home page and you&amp;#39;ll find a pinned post, this is the aforementioned &lt;a href=&#34;http://onigirionegai.info/post/about/&#34;&gt;about page&lt;/a&gt;. That page lists the sites that each of us now work on. Within a couple of clicks we now have a list of sub-sites. These were not even mentioned previously. It was up to each member to promote their personal sites even if they were hosted here. This is now no longer the case. So be sure to check them out! Now onto that last point that I mentioned just one paragraph ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-container-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;headline-4&#34;&gt;
We want websites for each project not one &amp;#34;one-size-fits-none&amp;#34; site
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;outline-text-headline-4&#34; class=&#34;outline-text-2&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the original idea of this site as a means of both introducing ourselves and our projects was not a bad one, it wasn&amp;#39;t the best. One over-arching site is just too big and any future projects we do come together for would simply be lost in a sea of other projects, especially if those projects are many and all large. Therefore, each project will have its own dedicated site that will be designed for its own identity. This, of course is something that will happen later. I mentioned we would &lt;em&gt;like&lt;/em&gt; to work on larger projects, but that is not possible at this time. If you would like to help though, I have information on how that could be possible on the &lt;a href=&#34;http://onigirionegai.info/post/about/&#34;&gt;most link page ever&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            </content>   
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/announcements" term="announcements" label="announcements" /> 
                                <category scheme="http://onigirionegai.info/tags/site" term="site" label="site" />
        </entry>
</feed>
